{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225610946","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225610946"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225611320","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225611320"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225611803","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225611803"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225612146","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225612146"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225612549","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225612548"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225613022","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225613022"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225613245","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225613245"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225616435","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225616435"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225616469","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225616469"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225617183","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225617183"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225617575","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225617575"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225617868","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225617868"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225618072","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225618072"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225618266","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225618266"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225618579","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225618579"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225618802","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225618802"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225621970","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225621970"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225622372","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225622372"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225624862","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225624862"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225625065","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225625065"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225625267","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225625267"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225628685","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225628685"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225632362","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225632362"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225633385","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225633385"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225636034","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225636034"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225636408","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225636407"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225636890","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225636890"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225637234","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225637234"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225637638","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225637638"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225638112","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225638112"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225638335","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225638335"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225641505","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225641505"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225641541","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225641540"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225642254","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225642254"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225642647","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225642647"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225642941","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225642941"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225643145","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225643145"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225643338","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225643338"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225643651","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225643651"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225643874","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225643874"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225646529","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225646529"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225646588","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225646587"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550225652875","data":{"timestamp":" 1550225652875"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_131315"," gameId":" ba1e2a0d-0ff6-4dcb-9a85-ac7ce4f313d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}